If you want to submit your data for archiving you need to be in the "Archive" tab.
Here you can find your current data packages that have not yet been archived
under the status "Active".
If your package is in this status, you can edit it at any time
by switching back to the "Editor" tab above.
To finalize your data for the submit, you need to add some organizational information.
Therefore, use the settings symbol right next to the book symbol.
Under "Legal", you have to agree to the necessary terms and conditions.
This includes that you have signed a data transfer agreement with your institution
prior to archiving and that any personal data in the package has been processed
in accordance with the relevant guidelines.
Once you have entered all of the necessary information, save your changes.
When your data package is ready to be reviewed by a data curator,
use the "Submit package" button at the top right.
As you can see, the status of your package has now changed
and you can find it under "In Review".
This means that your package is currently being reviewed by a curator.
While your package is in this status, you won´t be able to edit it.
The curator will return your data package for revision if there is a need to clarify
or if, for example, important metadata is missing.